{
    "wordBank": [
        {"number": 0, "zhuin": "ㄅ", "tailo": "p", "index": 0},
        {"number": 1, "zhuin": "ㄆ", "tailo": "ph", "index": 0},
        {"number": 2, "zhuin": "ㄇ", "tailo": "m", "index": 0},
        {"number": 3, "zhuin": "ㆠ", "tailo": "b", "index": 0},
        {"number": 4, "zhuin": "ㄍ", "tailo": "k", "index": 0},
        {"number": 5, "zhuin": "ㄎ", "tailo": "kh", "index": 0},
        {"number": 6, "zhuin": "ㄏ", "tailo": "h", "index": 0},
        {"number": 7, "zhuin": "ㆣ", "tailo": "g", "index": 0},
        {"number": 8, "zhuin": "ㄫ", "tailo": "ng", "index": 0},
        {"number": 9, "zhuin": "ㄐ", "tailo": "ts", "index": 0},
        {"number": 10, "zhuin": "ㄑ", "tailo": "tsh", "index": 0},
        {"number": 11, "zhuin": "ㄒ", "tailo": "s", "index": 0},
        {"number": 12, "zhuin": "ㆢ", "tailo": "j", "index": 0},
        {"number": 13, "zhuin": "ㄗ", "tailo": "ts", "index": 1},
        {"number": 14, "zhuin": "ㄘ", "tailo": "tsh", "index": 1},
        {"number": 15, "zhuin": "ㄙ", "tailo": "s", "index": 1},
        {"number": 16, "zhuin": "ㆡ", "tailo": "j", "index": 1}
    ],
    "part1": [
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 0, "sound": "p0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 3, "sound": "b0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 2, "sound": "m0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "這個怎麼唸？",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answerType": "sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 3, "buttonText": "<ruby>無<rt>？ㄜˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "bo5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 0, "buttonText": "<ruby>婆<rt>？ㄜˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "po5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 4, "sound": "k0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "text": "ㄏ", "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 7, "sound": "g0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "text": "ㄏ", "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "這個怎麼唸？",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answerType": "sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":7, "buttonText": "<ruby>𠢕<rt>？ㄠˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "gau5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "text": "ㄏ", "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":4, "buttonText": "<ruby>猴<rt>？ㄠˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "kau5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "text": "ㄏ", "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        }
        
    ],
    "part2": [
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 9, "sound": "ts0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 9, "text": "ㄐ", "sound": "ts0"},
                {"number": 10, "text": "ㄑ", "sound": "tsh0"},
                {"number": 11, "text": "ㄒ", "sound": "s0"},
                {"number": 12, "text": "ㆢ", "sound": "j0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 12, "sound": "j0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 9, "text": "ㄐ", "sound": "ts0"},
                {"number": 10, "text": "ㄑ", "sound": "tsh0"},
                {"number": 11, "text": "ㄒ", "sound": "s0"},
                {"number": 12, "text": "ㆢ", "sound": "j0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "這個怎麼唸？",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answerType": "sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 12, "text": "ㆢ"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 9, "sound": "ts0"},
                {"number": 10, "sound": "tsh0"},
                {"number": 11, "sound": "s0"},
                {"number": 12, "sound": "j0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 12, "buttonText": "<ruby>字<rt>？ㄧ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "ji7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 9, "text": "ㄐ", "sound": "ts0"},
                {"number": 10, "text": "ㄑ", "sound": "tsh0"},
                {"number": 11, "text": "ㄒ", "sound": "s0"},
                {"number": 12, "text": "ㆢ", "sound": "j0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 13, "sound": "ts1"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "text": "ㄗ", "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "text": "ㄘ", "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "text": "ㄙ", "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ", "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 16, "sound": "j1"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "text": "ㄗ", "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "text": "ㄘ", "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "text": "ㄙ", "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ", "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "這個怎麼唸？",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answerType": "sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 16, "buttonText": "<ruby>熱<rt>？ㄨㄚㆷ˙</rt></ruby>", "sound": "juah8"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "text": "ㄗ", "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "text": "ㄘ", "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "text": "ㄙ", "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ", "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 13, "buttonText": "<ruby>紙<rt>？ㄨㄚˋ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "tsua2"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "text": "ㄗ", "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "text": "ㄘ", "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "text": "ㄙ", "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ", "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        }
    ],
    "part3": [
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 8, "sound": "ng0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 4, "sound": "k0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 7, "sound": "g0"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "這個怎麼唸？",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answerType": "sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":8, "buttonText": "<ruby>硬<rt>？ㆤ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "nge7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":4, "buttonText": "<ruby>低<rt>？ㆤ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "ke7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":7, "buttonText": "<ruby>藝<rt>？ㆤ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "ge7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        }
    ],
    "review":[
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 3, "buttonText": "<ruby>無<rt>？ㄜˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "bo5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 0, "buttonText": "<ruby>婆<rt>？ㄜˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "po5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 0, "text": "ㄅ", "sound": "p0"},
                {"number": 1, "text": "ㄆ", "sound": "ph0"},
                {"number": 2, "text": "ㄇ", "sound": "m0"},
                {"number": 3, "text": "ㆠ", "sound": "b0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":7, "buttonText": "<ruby>𠢕<rt>？ㄠˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "gau5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "text": "ㄏ", "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":4, "buttonText": "<ruby>猴<rt>？ㄠˊ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "kau5"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 6, "text": "ㄏ", "sound": "h0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 12, "buttonText": "<ruby>字<rt>？ㄧ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "ji7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 9, "text": "ㄐ", "sound": "ts0"},
                {"number": 10, "text": "ㄑ", "sound": "tsh0"},
                {"number": 11, "text": "ㄒ", "sound": "s0"},
                {"number": 12, "text": "ㆢ", "sound": "j0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 16, "buttonText": "<ruby>熱<rt>？ㄨㄚㆷ˙</rt></ruby>", "sound": "juah8"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "text": "ㄗ", "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "text": "ㄘ", "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "text": "ㄙ", "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ", "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number": 13, "buttonText": "<ruby>紙<rt>？ㄨㄚˋ</rt></ruby>", "sound": "tsua2"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 13, "text": "ㄗ", "sound": "ts1"},
                {"number": 14, "text": "ㄘ", "sound": "tsh1"},
                {"number": 15, "text": "ㄙ", "sound": "s1"},
                {"number": 16, "text": "ㆡ", "sound": "j1"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":8, "buttonText": "<ruby>硬<rt>？ㆤ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "nge7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":4, "buttonText": "<ruby>低<rt>？ㆤ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "ke7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "你聽到什麼？",
            "questionType": "text sound button",
            "answerType": "text sound option",
            "answer": {"number":7, "buttonText": "<ruby>藝<rt>？ㆤ˫</rt></ruby>", "sound": "ge7"},
            "options": [
                {"number": 4, "text": "ㄍ", "sound": "k0"},
                {"number": 5, "text": "ㄎ", "sound": "kh0"},
                {"number": 8, "text": "ㄫ", "sound": "ng0"},
                {"number": 7, "text": "ㆣ", "sound": "g0"}
            ]
        }
    ]

}